A Guide to the David Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1010 FA453
Rockefeller Archive Center
David Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1010
1932-1994
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, David
Rockefeller, Peggy
FA453
4.6 Cubic Feet
Approximately 2,200 prints
Arrangement
Rockefeller family photographic holdings are arranged into the following series: Rockefeller family and Avery family photographs, Series 1001. William Avery Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1002. John D. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1003. William Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1004. John D. Rockefeller Jr. family photographs, Series 1005. Pocantico Hills photographs, Series 1006. John D. Rockefeller 3rd family photographs, Series 1007. Nelson A. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1008. Laurance S. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1009. David Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1010.
The David Rockefeller family photographs are further arranged in subseries by format - prints and oversized.
Other Finding Aids
For other Rockefeller family photographic holdings, please see the following finding aids:
FA445 Rockefeller family and Avery family photographs, Series 1001
FA446 William Avery Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1002
FA447 John D. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1003
FA448 William Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1004
FA449 John D. Rockefeller Jr. family photographs, Series 1005
FA450 Pocantico Hills photographs, Series 1006
FA451 John D. Rockefeller 3rd family photographs, Series 1007
FA454 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Series 1008
FA452 Laurance S. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1009
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
This series photographically documents David Rockefeller's life and career including his business activities, his philanthropic activities, government service and related events. The material also includes a wide variety of individual portraits and informal and candid shots of David Rockefeller, as well as individual and group portraits of his immediate family and relatives. The holdings also include a vast collection of David Rockefeller's travel as well as photographs of David with many business and political dignitaries and heads of state.
Photographs
- David Rockefeller family photographs, 1932-1994; 1010
  Arrangement
  For ease of access the material is further arranged by:
  Prints (Boxes P 1, P 2, P 3, etc.). Oversized (Boxes: O 1, O 2, O 3, C 1, C 2, C 3, etc.).
  - Prints, Approximately 2,165 prints
    - David Rockefeller family, 12 prints (Box P 156)
      Scope and Contents
      Primarily David Rockefeller as a baby and toddler.
    - Abby Rockefeller Halprin, 1949; 1 print (Box P 172, Folder 1)
    - Children, 9 prints (Box P 172, Folder 2)
    - Children, 1973; 5 prints (Box P 172, Folder 3)
    - DR - Art Collection - Fogg Art Museum - Harvard University, 1981; 3 prints (Box P 172, Folder 4)
    - DR - Art - Isao Ikegami, 1985; 1 print (Box P 172, Folder 5)
    - DR - Business - Africa, 16 prints (Box P 172, Folder 6)
    - DR - Business - Africa - Album 1, 16 prints (Box P 172, Folder 7)
    - DR - Business - Africa - Album 2, 20 prints (Box P 172, Folder 8)
    - DR - Business - Africa - Album 3, 20 prints (Box P 172, Folder 9)
    - DR - Business - Africa - Ivory Coast - Baoule Tribe, 1971; 2 prints (Box P 172, Folder 10)
    - DR - Business - Africa - South Africa, 1984; 1 print (Box P 172, Folder 11)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Brazil, 1986; 5 prints (Box P 172, Folder 12)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Brazil, 1988; 8 prints (Box P 172, Folder 13)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Brazil - Roberto Marinho, 1988; 4 prints (Box P 172, Folder 14)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Brian Mulroney, 1988; 2 prints (Box P 172, Folder 15)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Brian Mulroney, 1988; 1 print (Box P 172, Folder 16)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Brian Mulroney, 1988; 11 prints (Box P 172, Folder 17)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Caribbean Central American Action, 1987; 2 prints (Box P 172, Folder 18)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Council of the Americas - Ronald Reagan, 1985; 2 prints (Box P 172, Folder 19)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Council of the Americas, 1988; 3 prints (Box P 172, Folder 20)
      Ronald Reagan
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - George Bush, 1989 May; 8 prints (Box P 172, Folder 21)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - George Landau - Mario Vargas Llosa - Christopher Kennan, 1988; 1 print (Box P 172, Folder 22)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - H.E. Raul Alfonsin, 1988; 4 prints (Box P 172, Folder 23)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Inter-American Safety Council, 1988; 4 prints (Box P 172, Folder 24)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Jose Sarney, 1986; 9 prints (Box P 172, Folder 25)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Karsh Dinner, 1989; 1 print (Box P 172, Folder 26)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Mario Vargas Llosa1, 1988; 2 prints (Box P 172, Folder 27)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - President Sanguinetti of Uruguay, 1986; 7 prints (Box P 172, Folder 28)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Ronald Reagan, 1987; 2 prints (Box P 172, Folder 29)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Miguel de la Madrid, 1986; 9 prints (Box P 172, Folder 30)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Reception for Fernando Botero, 1988; 8 prints (Box P 172, Folder 31)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Venezuela, 1989; 2 prints (Box P 172, Folder 32)
    - DR - Business - Americas Society - Venezuela - Carlos Andres Perez, 1989; 3 prints (Box P 172, Folder 33)
    - DR - Business - Asia - China, 1986; 4 prints (Box P 173, Folder 34)
    - DR - Business - Asia - Japan, 4 prints (Box P 173, Folder 35)
    - DR - Business - Asia - Japan - Chase Manhattan Bank, 6 prints (Box P 173, Folder 36)
    - DR - Business - Asia - Japan - Dinner, 1988; 19 prints (Box P 173, Folder 37)
    - DR - Business - Asia - Japan - Keizo Saji, 1984; 9 prints (Box P 173, Folder 38)
    - DR - Business - Asia - Japan - Prime Minister Fukuda, 1978; 17 prints (Box P 173, Folder 39)
    - DR - Business - Asia - Japan - Teruhisa Noguchi, 1985; 24 prints (Box P 173, Folder 40)
    - DR - Business - Asia - Japan - Tokyo, 1988; 2 prints (Box P 173, Folder 41)
    - DR - Business - Asia - Japan - Yasushi Shidatsu, 1985; 3 prints (Box P 173, Folder 42)
    - DR - Business - Asia - Thailand - Bangkok, 1987; 6 prints (Box P 173, Folder 43)
    - DR - Business - Associates, 23 prints (Box P 173, Folder 44)
    - DR - Business - Associates, 2 prints (Box P 173, Folder 45)
    - DR - Business - Associates - Carol Bardasano, 1989; 1 print (Box P 173, Folder 46)
    - DR - Business - Associates - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1953; 1 print (Box P 173, Folder 47)
    - DR - Business - Associates - Chase Manhattan Bank, 15 prints (Box P 173, Folder 48)
    - DR - Business - Associates - Chase Manhattan Bank - Board of Directors, 1978; 2 prints (Box P 173, Folder 49)
    - DR - Business - Associates - Chase Manhattan Bank - Bonn, Germany, 1975; 1 prints (Box P 173, Folder 50)
    - DR - Business - Associates - Chase Manhattan Bank - Champion - McCloy, 1958; 1 print (Box P 173, Folder 51)
    - DR - Business - Associates - Chase Manhattan Bank - George Champion - Lawrence Marshall, 1961; 4 prints (Box P 173, Folder 52)
    - DR - Business - Associates - Chase Manhattan Bank - Golf Tournament, 1954; 2 prints (Box P 173, Folder 53)
    - DR - Business - Associates - Lawrence Marshall, 1955; 5 prints (Box P 173, Folder 54)
    - DR - Business - Associates - Salinas de Gortian, 16 prints (Box P 173, Folder 55)
    - DR - Business - Business and the Entrepreneurial American City Conference, 1988; 1 print (Box P 173, Folder 56)
    - DR - Business - Caux luncheon, 1988; 4 prints (Box P 173, Folder 57)
    - DR - Business - Chase National Bank, 1946; 3 prints (Box P 173, Folder 58)
    - DR - Business - Chase National Bank - Art Show, 1954; 1 print (Box P 173, Folder 59)
    - DR - Business - Chase Manhattan Bank - Africa Trip Reunion, 1982; 25 prints (Box P 173, Folder 60)
    - DR - Business - Chase Manhattan Bank - Building, 1963; 5 prints (Box P 173, Folder 61)
    - DR - Business - Chase Manhattan Bank - Dr. Abs, 1987; 1 print (Box P 173, Folder 62)
    - DR - Business - Chase Manhattan Bank - Equitable Life Assurance Society, 1 print (Box P 173, Folder 63)
    - DR - Business - Chase Manhattan Bank - Reception, 15 prints (Box P 173, Folder 64)
    - DR - Business - Chase Manhattan Bank - Sculpture - Group of Four Trees, 1972; 1 print (Box P 173, Folder 65)
    - DR - Business - Chase Manhattan Bank - Suggestion System, 1 print (Box P 173, Folder 66)
    - DR - Business - Council of the Americas - Texas, 1989; 1 print (Box P 173, Folder 67)
    - DR - Business - Council on Foreign Relations, 1985; 5 prints (Box P 173, Folder 68)
    - DR - Business - Council on Foreign Relations, 1985; 1 print (Box P 173, Folder 69)
    - DR - Business - Council on Foreign Relations - George Franklin, 1988; 4 prints (Box P 173, Folder 70)
    - DR - Business - Dartmouth Conference, 1979; 4 prints (Box P 174, Folder 71)
    - DR - Business - Dartmouth Conference - Kiev, 1971; 3 prints (Box P 174, Folder 72)
    - DR - Business - Dartmouth Conference - Leningrad, 1964; 5 prints (Box P 174, Folder 73)
    - DR - Business - Dartmouth Conference - XV, 1986; 20 prints (Box P 174, Folder 74)
    - DR - Business - Dartmouth Conference XVI, 1988; 2 prints (Box P 174, Folder 75)
    - DR - Business - Downtown Lower Manhattan Association, Inc., 1967; 1 print (Box P 174, Folder 76)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Czechoslovakia, 1975; 3 prints (Box P 174, Folder 77)
    - DR - Business - Europe - France, 1979; 5 prints (Box P 174, Folder 78)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Germany, 1972; 1 print (Box P 174, Folder 79)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Germany - Hermann Abs, 1987; 6 prints (Box P 174, Folder 80)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Hungary, 1989; 12 prints (Box P 174, Folder 81)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Hungary - Tamas Beck, 1989; 12 prints (Box P 174, Folder 82)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Italy - Council for the United States and Italy, 1988; 2 prints (Box P 174, Folder 83)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Poland, 1980; 1 print (Box P 174, Folder 84)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Poland - Council for the Development of Polish Agriculture, 1988; 7 prints (Box P 174, Folder 85)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Poland - Wojciech Jaruzelski, 1983; 3 prints (Box P 174, Folder 86)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Portugal - Lisbon, 1 print (Box P 174, Folder 87)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Portugal - Lisbon - Branch Opening, 20 prints (Box P 174, Folder 88)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Romania, 1973; 21 prints (Box P 174, Folder 89)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Spain - Kent Alessandro, 1986; 12 prints (Box P 174, Folder 90)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Sweden, 10 prints (Box P 174, Folder 91)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Switerland, Geneva, 1965 July 20; 17 prints (Box P 174, Folder 92)
    - DR - Business - Europe - Yugoslavia, 1973; 3 prints (Box P 174, Folder 93)
    - DR - Business - International Advisory Committee - Beijing, China, 1988; 21 prints (Box P 174, Folder 94)
    - DR - Business - International Advisory Committee - Princess Chulabhorn, 1988; 1 print (Box P 174, Folder 95)
    - DR - Business - Jim Patterson Group - Expo '86, 1986; 2 prints (Box P 174, Folder 96)
    - DR - Business - Latin America, 33 prints (Box P 175, Folder 97)
    - DR - Business - Latin America, 4 prints (Box P 175, Folder 98)
    - DR - Business - Latin America - Argentina, 1986; 11 prints (Box P 175, Folder 99)
    - DR - Business - Latin America - Brazil, 1967; Approximately 50 prints (Box P 175, Folder 100)
    - DR - Business - Latin America - Brazil - Jack E. Wyant, 1985; 2 prints (Box P 175, Folder 101)
    - DR - Business - Latin America - Chile - Banco de Estado de Chile, 1965; 23 prints (Box P 175, Folder 102)
    - DR - Business - Latin America - Dominican Republic, 1987; 1 print (Box P 175, Folder 103)
    - DR - Business - Latin America - Mexico, 1988; 14 prints (Box P 175, Folder 104)
    - DR - Business - Latin America - Uruguay, 1986; 4 prints (Box P 175, Folder 105)
    - DR - Business - Latin America - Uruguay, 1986; 24 prints (Box P 175, Folder 106)
    - DR - Business - Middle East, 3 prints (Box P 175, Folder 107)
    - DR - Business - Middle East, 1974; 5 prints (Box P 175, Folder 108)
    - DR - Business - Middle East - Lebanon, 1962; 7 prints (Box P 175, Folder 109)
    - DR - Business - Middle East - Lebanon, 1962; 31 prints (Box P 175, Folder 110)
    - DR - Business - Middle East - Lebanon - Dinner at Jean Aboujaoude, 1962; 29 prints (Box P 175, Folder 111)
    - DR - Business - Middle East - Lebanon - Emir Fouad Ghehab, 1962; 6 prints (Box P 175, Folder 112)
    - DR - Business - Middle East - Lebanon - Yerzeh, 1962; 51 prints (Box P 175, Folder 113)
    - DR - Business - Middle East - Morocco, 1979; 2 prints (Box P 175, Folder 114)
    - DR - Business - Middle East - Saudi Arabia, 1977; 1 print (Box P 175, Folder 115)
    - DR - Business - Middle East - Saudi Arabia - Crown Prince Fahd, 1976; 1 print (Box P 175, Folder 116)
    - DR - Business - Middle East - Saudi Arabia, 1 print (Box P 175, Folder 117)
    - DR - Business - Middle East - Turkey, 5 prints (Box P 175, Folder 118)
    - DR - Business - Middle East - Turkey, 1984; 6 prints (Box P 175, Folder 119)
    - DR - Business - Morningside Heights, Inc., 1950; 2 prints (Box P 175, Folder 120)
    - DR - Business - New York City Chamber of Commerce, 1988; 3 prints (Box P 175, Folder 121)
    - DR - Business - Partnership for New Jersey, 1986; 2 prints (Box P 175, Folder 122)
    - DR - Business - Stowaway Camp Saturday Luncheon, 1987; 1 print (Box P 175, Folder 123)
    - DR - Candids, 1 print (Box P 176, Folder 124)
    - DR - Candids, 1 print (Box P 176, Folder 125)
    - DR - Candids, Approx. 20 prints (Box P 176, Folder 126)
    - DR - Candids, 10 prints (Box P 176, Folder 127)
    - DR - Candids - American Horticultural Society, 1987; 2 prints (Box P 176, Folder 128)
    - DR - Candids - American Horticultural Society, 8 prints (Box P 176, Folder 129)
    - DR - Candids - Mr. Berthoin - Moscow, 1989; 1 print (Box P 176, Folder 130)
    - DR - Candids - Family of Man Dinner, 1965; 1 print (Box P 176, Folder 131)
    - DR - Candids - Golf - Chase Golf Outing in Pocantico Hills, 1981; 120 prints (Box P 176, Folder 132)
    - DR - Candids - Golf, 1971; 1 print (Box P 176, Folder 133)
    - DR - Candids - Golf, 1 print (Box P 176, Folder 134)
    - DR - Candids - Gracie Mansion, 1988; 2 prints (Box P 176, Folder 135)
    - DR - Candids - Greater San Francisco Chamber of Commerce - Fortune Magazine, 1968; 1 print (Box P 176, Folder 136)
    - DR - Candids - Harold Maeller, 1953; 5 prints (Box P 176, Folder 137)
    - DR - Candids - Iternational Monetary Fund (IMF) - Japan, 1987; 1 print (Box P 176, Folder 138)
    - DR - Candids - Interview of Eduardo Zeiger, 1981; 2 prints (Box P 176, Folder 139)
    - DR - Candids - La Guardia Dinner, 1982; 8 prints (Box P 176, Folder 140)
    - DR - Candids - La Guardia Medal, 6 prints (Box P 176, Folder 141)
    - DR - Candids - Latin American Dinner, 3 prints (Box P 176, Folder 142)
    - DR - Candids - Luncheon, 1987; 24 prints (Box P 176, Folder 143)
    - DR - Candids - New York Society of Systems Analysts, 1957; 1 print (Box P 176, Folder 144)
    - DR - Candids - Mr. and Mrs. Kenzeo Saji, 1987; 1 print (Box P 176, Folder 145)
    - DR - Candids - Pablo Cassals Concert, 1960; contact sheets (Box P 177, Folder 146)
    - DR - Candids - Rockefeller Center - Christmas, 1984; 4 prints (Box P 177, Folder 147)
    - DR - Candids - Service to Democracy Award, 1981; 3 prints (Box P 177, Folder 148)
    - DR - Candids - Staten Island Ferry, 1981; 5 prints (Box P 177, Folder 149)
    - DR - Candids, 1978; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 150)
    - DR - Candids, 1980; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 151)
    - DR - Candids, 1986; 3 prints (Box P 177, Folder 152)
    - DR - Candids, 1986; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 153)
    - DR - Candids - Americas Award, 1987; 6 prints (Box P 177, Folder 154)
    - DR - Candids - Bohemian Club Symphony Orchestra Concert, 1988; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 155)
    - DR - Candids - Buenos Aires, 1984; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 156)
    - DR - Candids - Business Tax Reform - Mario Cuomo, 1987; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 157)
    - DR - Candids - Canadian Executive Service Organization, 1987; 3 prints (Box P 177, Folder 158)
    - DR - Candids - Christmas - Family Lunch, 1986; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 159)
    - DR - Candids - Ecuador, 1987; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 160)
    - DR - Candids - Ed Koch, 1987; 2 prints (Box P 177, Folder 161)
    - DR - Candids - Forbes 75th Anniversary, 1987; 3 prints (Box P 177, Folder 162)
    - DR - Candids - Paris, 1987 (Box P 177, Folder 162A)
    - DR - Candids - Peggy Rockefeller on Boat, 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 162B)
    - DR - Candids - Peru, 1987; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 162C)
    - DR - Dignitaries, 35 prints (Box P 177, Folder 163)
    - DR - Dignitaries, Negatives (Box P 177, Folder 164)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Akio Morita, 1991 November; 18 prints (Box P 177, Folder 165)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Aleksandr Yakovlev, 1988; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 166)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Ambassador Peter Jay, 1980; 3 prints (Box P 177, Folder 167)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Austria - Hannes Androsch, 7 prints (Box P 177, Folder 168)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Brian Mulroney, 1985; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 169)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Eddie Fenech Adami, Prime Minister of Malta, 1987; 2 prints (Box P 177, Folder 170)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Ferdinand Marcos, 1982; 2 prints (Box P 177, Folder 171)
    - DR - Dignitaries - George Shultz, 1989; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 172)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Giscard d' Estaing - Gerald Ford, 1974; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 173)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Giscard d' Estaing - Paris, 1989; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 174)
    - DR - Dignitaries - H.S. Rew, 1981; 4 prints (Box P 177, Folder 175)
    - DR - Dignitaries - India, 1978; 11 prints (Box P 177, Folder 176)
    - DR - Dignitaries - King Juan Carlos of Spain, 1985; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 177)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Mikail Gorbachev - White House, 1987; 5 prints (Box P 177, Folder 178)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Morocco - Fete du Throne, 1986; 7 prints (Box P 177, Folder 179)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Nancy Reagan - Prince Franz Josef II - White House, 1985; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 180)
    - DR - Dignitaries - NAR - Kosciusko-Morizet, 1977; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 181)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Pope John Paul II, 1983; 9 prints (Box P 177, Folder 182)
    - DR - Dignitaries - President Diouf - Kykuit, 64 prints (Box P 177, Folder 183)
    - DR - Dignitaries - President Machel, 26 prints (Box P 177, Folder 184)
    - DR - Dignitaries - President - Jorge Pacheo Areco - Uruguay, 1971; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 185)
    - DR - Dignitaries - President Wasmosi - Paraguay, 1994; 1 print (Box P 177, Folder 186)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Ronald Reagan - Republican Senatorial Inner Circle, 1986 (Box P 178, Folder 187)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Ronald Reagan, 1982 (Box P 178, Folder 188)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Ronald Reagan (Box P 178, Folder 189)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Ronald Reagan, 1985 (Box P 178, Folder 190)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Ronald Reagan - Kykuit, 1986 (Box P 178, Folder 191)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Ronald Reagan, 1988 (Box P 178, Folder 192)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Prime Minister Suzuki, 1981 (Box P 178, Folder 193)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Prince Bernard, 1975 (Box P 178, Folder 194)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Princess Chulabhorn, 1989 (Box P 178, Folder 195)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Queen Elizabeth, 1976 (Box P 178, Folder 196)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Queen of Siam - Kykuit, 1980 February 9 (Box P 178, Folder 197)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Slobodan Milosevic, 1980 (Box P 178, Folder 198)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Spain, 1987 (Box P 178, Folder 199)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Prince of Asturias - Freedom Prize, 1986 (Box P 178, Folder 200)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Thailand - Royal family - Knight Grand Cross, 1987 (Box P 178, Folder 201)
    - DR - Dignitaries - Thailand - Royal family - Knight Grand Cross, 1987 (Box P 178, Folder 202)
    - DR - Education - Harvard - 50th Reunion, 1986 (Box P 178, Folder 203)
    - DR - Education - Harvard - International Dinner, 1987 (Box P 178, Folder 204)
    - DR - Education - Harvard - Reunion, 1981 (Box P 178, Folder 205)
    - DR - Education - Lincoln School Class of 1932 (Box P 178, Folder 206)
    - DR - Education - London School of Economics (Box P 178, Folder 207)
    - DR - Education - University of Chicago, 1950 (Box P 178, Folder 208)
    - DR - Government Service - Business Council of New York State, 1982 (Box P 178, Folder 209)
    - DR - Government Service - Inter-Executive Service Corps, 1964 (Box P 178, Folder 210)
    - DR - Government Service - President's Commission on Executive Exchange (Box P 178, Folder 211)
    - DR - Government Service - Trilateral Commission (Box P 178, Folder 212)
    - DR - Government Service - Trilateral Commission - Mexico, 1987 (Box P 178, Folder 213)
    - DR - Government Service - Trilateral Commission, 1974 (Box P 178, Folder 214)
    - DR - Government Service - Trilateral Commission - Prime Minister Nakasone, 1988 (Box P 178, Folder 215)
    - DR - Informals - Chase Manhattan Bank (Box P 178, Folder 216)
    - DR - Informals - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1971 (Box P 178, Folder 217)
    - DR - Informals - Ed Koch - Brooke Astor (Box P 178, Folder 218)
    - DR - Informals - Interstate North Office Park, 1982 (Box P 178, Folder 219)
    - DR - Informals - Rockefeller Center - Lighting Rockefeller Center's Christmas Tree, 1982 (Box P 178, Folder 220)
    - DR - Informals - Rockefeller Center - Radio City Music Hall 50th Anniversary, 1982 (Box P 178, Folder 221)
    - DR - Memorabilia - Advertising Council Public Service Award, 1971 (Box P 178, Folder 222)
    - DR - Philanthropies, 1944-1961; 14 prints (Box P 156)
    - DR - Philanthropies - American Assembly - Sandra Day O'Connor, 1982 (Box P 178, Folder 223)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Arkansas Arts Center, 1963 (Box P 178, Folder 224)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Christian A. Herter Memorial Award, 1981 (Box P 178, Folder 225)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 8 prints (Box P 179, Folder 226)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Cite Internationale Universitaire de Paris, 1987; 16 prints (Box P 179, Folder 227)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Cite Internationale Universitaire de Paris, 1987; 20 prints (Box P 179, Folder 228)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Harlem Week Economic Development Luncheon, 1983; 18 prints (Box P 179, Folder 229)
    - DR - Philanthropies - International House, 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 230)
    - DR - Philanthropies - International House - Gerald Ford - Gordon Evans, 1987; 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 231)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Lincoln Center - Glenn Ferguson, 1983; 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 232)
    - DR - Philanthropies - Museum of Modern Art, 1986; 1 print (Box P 179, Folder 233)